

Uriel Cid Computer Systems Engineer

🔘 Tijuana, Baja California

☑ cidsantos56@gmail.com

% 663-222-4063

SOCIAL

in @cidsantos

PROFILE

Hello World, I am graduated from the Universidad del Valle de Orizaba in Veracruz and with experience in customer service and attention to problem solving. Web Developer. As any Systems Engineer, the areas covered by my profile range from maintenance, development, and execution, as well as support and training in technologies.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree computer systems

Universidad del Valle de Orizaba 2015 - 2021

Diplomat: Development of Web 3.0

Universidad del Valle de Orizaba 2021 - 2021

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS
- PHP, Python
- Databases
- Linux, MacOs
- GitHub
- Ubiquiti Antennas

EXPERIENCE

🖣 WISP Manager

From 2018 to 2021 | Independent WISP

Wireless Internet Service Provider Manager, this was a personal project to deliver Internet to people in a underdeveloped town. The project was a success.

🖣 Technical support specialist

From 2018 to 2019 | Sitel Mexico

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds. The company is dedicated to DirecTV users in the United States.

PHP Legacy Developer

From 2020 to 2021 | Universidad del Valle de Orizaba

Work for my alma matter supporting legacy projects and develop new functionalities. Server maintenance and updates based on Centos GNU/Linux distribution.

Django developer

From 2022 to 2022 | Integriappp

Experienced in integrating Django-based applications with databases and external APIs. Skilled at debugging and troubleshooting issues. Strong problem-solving skills and ability to work independently or as part of a team.

Support Engineer

From 2022 to 2023 | ASIT TJ

Responsible for providing technical assistance to customers or end users. This include answering questions, troubleshooting problems, and helping to resolve issues with software or hardware.

REFERENCES

Mag. Developer

Dr. Monserrat Sanchez

Phone: 272-130-7151

Email: sise@correo.univo.edu.mx

Mag. Developer

Mr. Miguel Mendez

Phone: 484-370-9357

Email: mcinova13@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

SpanishEnglish

INTERESTS









Music Travel

Read

Coocking